Speaker 0: Hello, Amy.
Speaker 0: I'm Dr.
Speaker 0: Jones.
Speaker 0: How are you doing today?
Speaker 1: I'm okay, but it hurts when I go to the bathroom when I pee.
Speaker 0: That's called dysuria, and it's pretty common.
Speaker 0: When did this start?
Speaker 1: Two days ago.
Speaker 0: Have you taken anything for it?
Speaker 1: I tried some Tylenol and drank cranberry juice.
Speaker 1: It helped.
Speaker 0: Have you had this before?
Speaker 1: Yes, I had this several years ago before you were my doctor.
Speaker 1: Do you remember about what year that was?
Speaker 0: I think it was... Okay.
Speaker 1: How was it treated back then?
Speaker 0: The clinic gave me an antibiotic, Bactrim, and that made it better.
Speaker 0: Great.
Speaker 1: Is there any chance that you're pregnant?
Speaker 0: I use protection, but there's always a chance, I guess.
Speaker 0: And so when was your last menstrual period?
Speaker 0: Three weeks ago.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: I think we should check her pregnancy test just to be sure.
Speaker 0: Have you had any vomiting, nausea, abdominal pain, back pain, shortness of breath, blood in your urine, constipation, diarrhea, or skin rashes?
Speaker 0: Yes, I've had abdominal pain down low.
Speaker 0: And any vaginal discharge or drainage or painful intercourse?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 1: Okay.
Speaker 0: Do you have any other problems that you'd like me to address?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: I would like to do a simple physical exam and have you give us a urine sample.
Speaker 0: I will order both a pregnancy test and a urine test and that we will do now and determine treatment when we have the results.
Speaker 0: Does that sound okay to you?